<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://ashleyshine.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 13:01:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ashleyshine.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ashleyshine.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 13:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleyshine.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Currently at Factual, where I work on data science and engineering problems with geospatial data.
Previously at Ticketmaster, where I worked on the personalized recommendations team.
I studied Applied Math &amp;amp; Statistics at UCLA.
In my spare time you can find me cycling, shopping at Trader Joes, or attempting to complete the NYT mini crossword.
You can also find me on Github and LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Three Years of Running</title>
      <link>https://ashleyshine.github.io/posts/strava-viz-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleyshine.github.io/posts/strava-viz-running/</guid>
      <description>All the code for this project can be found on github.
If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, then you&amp;rsquo;ve probably used Strava at some point to track your runs. If you also spend a lot of time staring at maps like me, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably also realized that&amp;rsquo;s a treasure trove of geospatial data. Welcome to&amp;hellip;a way to create quick and beautiful visualizations of Strava data.
Sections  Motivation Static Heatmaps Facet Plots Interactive Heatmaps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of None Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://ashleyshine.github.io/posts/master-of-none/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleyshine.github.io/posts/master-of-none/</guid>
      <description>All the code for this project is available on github.
Things I have wanted to do for a while and finally found time to do:
 rewatch Master of None play around with some natural language processing (NLP)  Things I also did:
 natural language processing with Master of None scripts  The episode scripts used for this analysis were scraped from Springfield! Springfield! Movie &amp;amp; TV Show Scripts using download-scripts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Did My Time Go? Fall 2017 Edition</title>
      <link>https://ashleyshine.github.io/posts/fall-2017-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleyshine.github.io/posts/fall-2017-analysis/</guid>
      <description>All the code for this project is available on github.
&amp;lsquo;Twas the night (ten days) before Christmas&amp;hellip; when I finished fall quarter finals, came home for Winter Break, looked at my calendar, and realized something crazy - I had, for once, free time! To do whatever I wanted! Imagine that. Then I realized I also had something else: because I time-block with my calendar (Google Calendar to be specific) in order to plan and protect my time, I had (unknowingly) generated a detailed dataset on how I&amp;rsquo;ve spent my time in over the past year or two.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>